const CrimeAgainstWomen = [
	{
		questionText: 'Which of the following kind of cases are registered high against women in India?',
		ans: ['Cruelty by husband and relatives'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Which of the  State has recorded more no of violent incidents on women in India as per NCRB 2021',
		ans: ['U.P'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'The Protection of Women from Domestic Violence Act',
		ans: ['2005'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'The commission of Sati(prevention) Act',
		ans: ['1987'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'The Prohibition of Child Marriage Act',
		ans: ['2006'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Hindu Widow Remarriage Act ',
		ans: ['1856'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Medical Termination of Pregnancy Act ',
		ans: ['1971'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Suppression of Immoral Traffic in Women and Girls Act(SITA Act)',
		ans: ['1956 '],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Sharadha Act came into force on',
		ans: ['April 1, 1930'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Dowry Prohibition Act was enacted in the',
		ans: ['1961'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Dowry Prohibition Act was amended in the year',
		ans: ['1986'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Prohibition of Child Marriage Act was enacted in the year?',
		ans: ['2006'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'What is the punishment under Prohibition of Child Marriage Act?',
		ans: ['2 years of imprisonment'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Hindu Marriage Act was enacted in the year?',
		ans: ['1995'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'The Muslim women (Protection of Rights on Marriage) Act was introduced in the year?',
		ans: ['2019'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Practicing Triple Talaq is prohibited in',
		ans: ['2018'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Shahara Banu case is related to',
		ans: ['Compensation'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Punishment for practicing Triple Talaq is',
		ans: ['3 years of imprisonment'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'The Hindu Adoption and Maintenance Act was enacted in the year?',
		ans: ['1958'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'The Indian Divorce Act was introduced in the year?',
		ans: ['1869'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Dissolution of Muslim Marriage Act was enacted in the year?',
		ans: ['1939'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'PCPNDT Act was introduced in the year',
		ans: ['1993'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'PCPNDT Act full form',
		ans: ['Pre-Conception and Pre-Natal Diagnostic Techniques (PCPNDT) Act '],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Which IPC section deals with Cruelty by Husband',
		ans: ['IPC 498A'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'The Indecent Representation of Women (Prohibition) Act, was enacted in the year',
		ans: ['1986'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'The Protection of Women from Domestic Violence Act was enacted in the year?',
		ans: ['2005'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'The Protection of Women from Domestic Violence Act was come into force from?',
		ans: ['26th Oct, 2006'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'which committe is formed on Nirbhaya incident',
		ans: ['JJ Verma'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Sexual Harassment of Women at Workplace (Prevention, Prohibition and Redressa Act was introduced in the year?',
		ans: ['2013'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Vishaka Guidelines are related to',
		ans: ['Child marriage'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Which IPC section deals with Dowery Death',
		ans: ['IPC 304B'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Which of the following Act is related to mechanism of Internal Complaints Committee?',
		ans: ['Sexual Harassment at Work Place Act'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'When did International Day for the Elimination of Violence against Women was celebrated?',
		ans: ['November 25th'],
	},
];
export default CrimeAgainstWomen;
